-♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ Next Sunday, A.D.
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses didn't like him
so they shot him into space ♪
♪♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can find
-♪ La-la-la
-♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
-♪ La-la-la
-♪ Now, keep in mind,
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
-♪ La-la-la
-♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends
♪♪
♪ Robot roll call
-Cambot!
-Pan left!
-Gypsy!
-Hi, girl!
-Tom Servo!
-What a cool guy!
-Cro-o-o-o-o-w!
-He's a wisecracker.
-♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
-♪ La-la-la
-♪ Then repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax"
♪ For "Mystery Science
Theater 3000" ♪
[Doors thud and creak]
[Doors whir]
[Doors thud and clank]
-30 seconds to commercial sign.
-Hi, everybody.
Welcome to
the Satellite of Love.
I'm Joel.
I'm still trapped in outer space
and, uh, still trying to
maintain my sunny disposition.
As you can see, I've redecorated
the Satellite of Love.
So, if I ever do make it
off this satellite
and get back to Earth,
I can do a talk show panel,
you know.
-Commercial sign in 15 seconds.
-Crow made this, uh,
batch of brownies here,
and, uh, we're gonna
be enjoying those.
Uh, we ran out of milk, though.
We'll probably have
to use Tang...
-Ick.
-...to drink with them.
-Commercial sign in 5...
4...3...2.
Commercial sign now.
-Uh, don't go away.
We'll be right back.
If you do have to go away,
just come back
in a couple of minutes.
Uh, my guest will be
Tom Servo and the amazing Crow.
♪♪
-Oh, man, Crow,
these were great brownies,
but we haven't
had brownie fixings
around here for a long time.
What were they?
-Uh, uh, uh, hey.
Is that a new jumpsuit, Joel?
Oh, we got, uh,
the scientists calling.
-Phew.
-Look oppressed.
-Come in, Joel,
my little bagel with a schmear.
-Hey, sirs. Uh,
w-what's up?
-Our income if
this new gig works out.
-Yes, Larry and I have
developed a new chain
of fast-food restaurants
with very low overhead
because we don't cook our food.
-'Cause frying and broiling
takes out a lot
of the nutrients.
-Yes, uh, if your body
likes another body,
why don't you try one
of our burgers, au natural.
It's, uh, ripped from the bone
to your plate in seconds.
It's Clay and Lar's Flesh Barn.
[Both laugh]Uh, make with the lyrics, Larry.
-Okay.
♪ If you're tired
of the same-old fare ♪
♪ You got a friend
in Clay and Lar ♪
♪ All our meat
is guaranteed rare ♪
♪ Because we don't cook it
-You see, cooking takes out
all the flavor.
-♪ If you're tired
of cooking at home ♪
♪ Try our meat
right off the bone ♪
♪ If you listen,
you can hear it moan ♪
♪ Because we don't cook it
-Stunned, killed
right at your table,
eviscerated very fresh.
-♪ Now, there's no need
for you to drive through ♪
♪ Our fresh meat
will walk out to you ♪
♪ You'll say, "Hi,"
he'll say, "Moo" ♪
♪ It's Clay and Lar's
Flesh Barn ♪
-15 locations to serve you,
now in Altoona.
-Oh, well, uh, what
I have this week is,
I was just -- got --
got kind of bored
in the bathroom,
and I made this.
It's, uh --
As you can see,
it's, uh --
built a roll of toilet paper
in a 2-liter bottle.
What do you think, sirs?
-Great.
-Yeah.
-You could use it
for a Molotov cocktail
or something.
[Laughs]
-Aw, you guys twist everything.
You could've made
tiddlywinks evil.
-Thank you!
Well, your film this week,
Joel, is a little number
called "Women of
the Prehistoric Planet."
There's really no reason for it.
It just is what it is.
Deal with it, musky breath.
-Enjoy!
[Rumbling, alarm blares]
-Oh, my God!
-Whoa!
-Aah!
♪♪
I still think that toilet paper
was a good idea.
-I just don't understand it.
-"Women of
the Prehistoric Planet."
My sister saw this
in junior high.
All the boys had
to go into the gym.
♪♪
-Wendell Corey.
-Man among men.
-John Agar.
-We wish you a Merry Anders.
-Hmm.
-Let's see.
Kam Tong.
Kam Tong races.
-Oh.
You are here.
-Yep.
♪♪
-Oh, what's that, Servo?
-I think it's the...
creamy nougat center
of the Milky Way, uh, galaxy.
-Oh.
-There's the caramel
constellation.
-It's so beautiful.
Looks like crud on a windshield.
-It's a cosmic sneeze.
-That -- That's beautiful.
♪♪
Hey, look, it's,
uh, Lady Remington.
-Looks like tin foil.
-It's a steam iron.
-Nah, it's a biscuit warmer.
-It's a, uh, chrome watermelon.
-It's a metal football.
♪♪
-It's one of Gallagher's hats.
-It's any piece of alternative
reality we choose it to be.
-That's no alternative
piece of reality.
That's a battle station!
-Make an entry in the log book.
-A big one.
-On this day,
lead command ship Cosmos I...
-You know, he must hit his head
on that beam all the time.
-...6 months, 18 days...
-Probably doesn't
even feel it anymore.
-Cosmos IIand III
are following in three-month
intervals, as programmed.
-Looks like a great,
big Erector Set.
-We continue homeward bound
without incident.
-Talking to ourselves.
-Well, Doc, you better dust
off your dress uniform.
-The strapless one?
-You'll soon be home.
-Ha.
Commander,
you've been saying that
for the past six months.
-That's the biggest
problematic bubble
I think I've ever seen.
-Nah, I think it looks likea big Joe Namath Popcorn Popper.
-Ba-dum.
-Positive.
-That's the biggest
guitar I've ever seen
built right into the wall
behind them.
-...32 minutes to go.
-Might as well be a year.
That's how long it seems
since we left Centaurus.
-Thanks for the exposition.
-Excuse me, Doc.
That one month and 12 days
Commander Scott just mentioned,
is that our time here
in space or time at home?
-Uh, you're new here,
aren't you, Elvis?
-It's about six years back home.
-Six more years.
Brother.
-Thank you, Colonel.
-You know something, sir.
We've been gone so long,
my kid brother is now
30 years older than me.
[Chuckles]
Is that crazy?
-That's what happens whenyou travel at near optic speeds.
-It's kooky, Colonel.
-I suppose in some ways,
it is crazy.
-Imagine what would happen
if a married guy came home
after five years
and found his wife
was an old woman.
-Oh, I don't even
wanna think about that!
-It's not funny, Corporal.
-...can't qualifyfor cosmic expedition, Sergeant.
[Devices beeping]
Distress signal from Cosmos III.
-You have your coordinates,
Mr. Scott.
Try to get an accurate fix
on their position.
-I'll work on getting
these chicks hatched.
-Communications -- King.
-Uh, communications queen.
Come in.
-...Cosmos III.
-Yes, sir.
Clearing all channels.
-Yes, your highness.
-I have a fix on Cosmos III,
Admiral.
-How do you barre chord again?
-They're here in
the Solaris star system.
-They're over by
E minor or C sharp.
-It could be a dangerous area
to be off-course.
Solaris is a new star
surrounded by numerous planets
and a great deal of cosmic gas.
-Must be from the cosmic chili.
-...gas clouds
at full acceleration,
they'll burn up in an instant.
-And we'll be there to watch.
[Beeping continues]
-Communications,
anything from Cosmos III?
-Nothing yet, Admiral.
We have all channels wide open.
-Try to contact them.
I'll be right in.
Sergeant, reduce speed 1/8th.
-And try to pretend
that meant something.
-There's no sense in
getting the gap between us
any wider than possible.
-Yes, sir.
-The what?
-The gap between our ears.
-Prepare to reduce programmed
acceleration by 1/8th.
-Think they're gonna
be the comic relief?
I just got a feeling.
Did you hear what I heard,
Mr. Bradley?
We're reducing speed.
-I heard.
-They're pretty well-groomed
for having been in space
for so long.
-...all this time.
-Not with Scott navigating.
He knows where we were,
where we are,
and where we're going to be
at any given moment --
past, present, or future.
-And all from
the horoscope charts
he got from Nancy Reagan.
-I'll, uh...
I'll check it out.
Stand by, Chief.
-Activate maneuver.
-[Clicking tongue]
-Now, don't tell me
he's thinking of turning back.
-Uh, he's thinking
of turning back.
-What would you do?
-Turn back.
-There are 20 people
and the valuable cargo
of gravitide
aboard that ship.
There is responsibility.
Correction, Doc.
There are 12 men and the cargo
aboard the Cosmos III.
The rest are Centaurians.
-Oh, yes, yes.
-They're all wearing Dickies.
-You, uh...
You don't consider
Centaurians people,
do you, Scott?
-I don't think we should put so
much trust in them, that's all.
-Let's lock them all
in relocation camps.
-Hey, it's Pink Lady.
-Centaurians once had
a very high culture, Scott.
-And Jeff.-They could again with our help.
-You sound exactly
like the Admiral.
-And you sound
like Archie Bunker.
-...here so long, your sense
of values have changed.
-A deep-space colony
can't always live
by the standards
we do back home.
-Admiral King's theory
of cosmic colonization.
-Is that a Ray Stevens song?
-It was required reading
at the academy, Dr. Farrell.
Commander, if you try
getting to know the admiral,
you might discover
he's quite a remarkable man.
-And really quite stunning
when you think about it.
-I've been with him on Centaurusfor the past three years.
-La-de-da.-I think I know him pretty well.
-And you're no Jack Kennedy,
senator.
-...almost 20 years.
-Infectious.
-I belive I know him better.
-Yeah, well, my dad
can beat up your dad.
Ha!
-Cosmos fleet command ship one
to Cosmos III.
-Disinflating Annette's hair,
starting on my mark.
-...if you are receiving,
please acknowledge.
-Shall we keep trying, sir?
-Cosmos III,it's Admiral King.
If you are receiving,
please advise Captain Ross
that he's off-course and
approaching a dangerous area.
Repeat --
Your present course will
take you into a danger zone.
-What?
-Keep trying.
Repeat the same message
on all the channels.
-In your voice, sir?
-Admiral King.
Do you think something
has happened to them?
-We don't know yet, Linda.
-I have friends aboard
the Cosmos III.
I am afraid for them.
-We all have friends
on Cosmos III.
We're all deeply concerned.
-So concerned that I felt
compelled to touch you.
-Cosmos fleet command ship one
to Cosmos III.
-Pigs...in...spaaace!
-Great gag.
-Cosmos Ito Cosmos III.
If you can transmit,
please acknowledge.
-Jang,
you've got to listen to me.
Both of you.
Put away those guns.
It'll soon be too late.
-No.
-No way, old man.
-Can't you understand,
this ship is out of control!
Unless you release those men
in the maneuvering room,
we're going nowhere
but to our death!
-You're trying to trick us,
Captain.
-I am not trying to --
-You, Lieutenant. Anderson.
You will take us
back to Centaurus.
-You stupid fools.
-It's pronounced Centaurus.
-He said the Centaurians
couldn't be trusted.
-Jang, what are you doing?
-Think of us as Klingons
without the Kling.
-...turning back to Centaurus.
-Chang, this is treasonous.
Give me the gun.
[Rumbling]
-A very strong
magnetic field, sir.
We're locked in.
-It's one of the planets
of Solaris.
We've entered
it's field of gravity.
-Activate the decelerator,
Sergeant.
-What does it mean, Captain?
-It's no use.
-It means that we're doomed --
crash into that planet
unless I can regain control
of the maneuvering room.
-All: Not again!
-And that playground ball
is a threat, too.
-Then we shall crash.
It is better that we die...
-Woop.
-...than be your slaves.
-We have never treated you
as a slave.
-Yeah, what about that one time?
-The captain knows
one of the b--
-Imperial dog.
-...activate
the gravity compensator!
♪♪
-We're gonna crash
into a Universal picture!
♪♪
-Fakey.
-All: Fakey.
-Real.
-Dead guy.
-All: Fakey.
-Real.
-Real fakey.
-Fake guys.
-Filmed on location,
in Tommy Ronick's front yard.
♪♪
-They're hammered.
-And the chicks are dead.
[Whirring]
-Bzzz.
-What do you suppose
happened to them, Admiral?
-Ah, they probably crashed
in Tommy's front yard.
-Magnetic fields.
Cosmic clouds.
-Yellow moons, pinks hearts,
all that stuff.
-It shouldn't.
-I wonder how they got
so far off course.
I mean, it's impossible
they didn't know.
-No question about it, Admiral.
They're grounded on one of
the inner planets of Solaris.
-Yikes.
-Communications.
Anything coming in?
-No, Admiral.
Nothing but the homing signal.
-Any reply from
Command Headquarters?
-Nothing yet, Admiral.
-Keep me informed.
-Well, that's not gonna be easy.You're kind of a muttonhead.
[Devices beeping]
-The admiral is really upset,
isn't he?
-Hmm.
-Yeah.
-First ship he's ever lost.
-Lost his keys a few times,
but never a whole ship.
-Do you think
he would turn back?
-Probably.
He's kind of a coward.
-If High Command will let him,
he will.
-Hmm. I don't think so.
-We're too close to home.
-You know we'll never get there.
It is just a wishful dream.
-I know what you mean, honey.
-Uh-oh.
-Six months of all
this pressurized...
-Moron patrol.
-...isn't exactly
what I'd call a pleasure party.
-Well, it could be, sugar,
if you'd let yourself go.
-Well, well,
the wolf of outer space.
And who let you out
of your darkened den?
-Now, be kind to me, ladies.
Don't forget that
I'm your ingenious engineer,
the master
of the maneuvering room
and the activator
of your gravitators.
-Not to mention
a flagellating butthead.
-...be no ups or downs.
-Here we go again.
-Well, I suppose we are gratefulfor all these amazing services,
Mr. Bradley.
-Lieutenant, you just allow
this sweet thing
a few moments liberty
with your old star mate,
and, uh...
well, I'll consider
you all paid in full.
-He's done everything,
but insult a Centaurian.
-N-Now, Lieutenant,
there's no reason
for you to treat me like
a common old Centaurian.
-Oh.
-Oops.
-Hey, Linda, I'm sorry.
Well, now, you know I didn't
mean anything by what I said.
-Nooo.
♪♪
-You know me,
I could light up a whole room.
[Laughs]
Just by walking out.
-Yaaay.
♪♪
-Forget it, Linda.
He didn't mean it.
-You know, she's right.
I mean, Lieutenant Bradley's
crazy about you.
-Hey, check out those
space-age lockers.
-You know that.
-Yes, I know.
But I wonder if your people
really canaccept us, Karen.
-Listen, Linda,
y-you have an exciting
new life ahead of you.
Why, don't worry
about being accepted.
-'Cause you won't be.
-When you get around all those
young cadets at the academy,
you'll forget
all about Centaurus
and those years in the colony
and people with narrow minds.
-Among other things.
-You know, I've never even
see a boy of my own age.
-I'm resetting the controls
so they crash into
the prehistoric planet.
-Command headquarters.
[Chiming]
[Device beeps]
-Do I look good up here?
-The reply from Space Command,
Mr. Scott.
-It says, "Do not tear,
spindle, or mutilate."
-Communique from Headquarters,
Admiral.
-Looks like your agent's not
gonna get you out of this one.
-"Since no other communications
can be established,
it must be assumed
that Cosmos IIIhas crashed,
killing all crew members
and passengers."
-He's right.
-"Regret your requestto return to star system Solaris
to search for survivors
must be denied."
-Signed by Zippy the Chimp.
-Sorry, sir.
-Huh?
-It would've been
a futile effort, Admiral.
-We will reverse our course,
Mr. Scott.
Program our flight plan
to take us to Solaris.
-But sir,
the request had been denied
by Command Headquarters.
-I'm the commander
of this fleet!
All the passengers
and crewmen on these ships
are my responsibilityas long as we are in deep space.
We are still in space.
-Well, they're
in deep something.
-Is that clear, Mr. Scott?
-Hold me.
-Yes, sir.
-I mean Mr...
-Get a communique
to Command Headquarters
to that effect immediately.
-Nevins, stand by
to reverse course.
Horizontal maneuver.
-Yes, sir.
-That's how he got that job.
-Maneuvering room,
this is controls.
Stand by horizontal activators
for a change in course.
-And beam up more depth.
-Maneuvering room standing by.
-I'll talk to you later, sugar.
-I just made out on the phone.
This is great!
-Well, what is all this,
Mr. Bradley?
First we slow down to a walk...
-It's a control panel.
You should know that.
-Looks like
we're going back, Chief.
-You mean Space Command
okayed the old man's request?
-Well, if they didn't,
he's sure gonna catch it
when we doget home.
-Maneuvering room from Control.
New course is 1-7-5 degrees
on horizontal plane.
-1-7-5 horizontal.
[Clacking]
Program.
-That's all you have to do?
I could have done that.
-...on Cosmos III'shoming beam
for three month's cruising.
Full acceleration.
-Three months?
Ye-- Yes, sir.
-I got this
Snoopy ruler for free.
What do you think, Tom?
Anybody?
Somebody.
-Activate maneuver.
♪♪
-People always seem
to comfort her.
♪♪
-Even our name
says Merry Christmas!
♪♪
-Gilligan!
-Skipper!
Mary Anne!
-Ginger!
-Thurston?
-Lovey!
-Wrong way.
-Japanese guy!
♪♪
-Hey, the mummy's
getting better.
♪♪
[Bird squawking in distance]
-We'll stop here for the night.
At least it's dry ground.
-Yeah, rest here.
Maybe we can find your scalp.
Hey, here's some mossy lichen.
We can make a wig
out of it for ya.
-Don't touch me!
I told you to stay away from me.
-I only want to help you,
Lieutenant.
You need help.
-Yeah,
but you put my arm in a sling
and it doesn't even hurt.
-...none of us
wouldn't need any help.
-I'm sorry for
what has happened,
but Ididn't rebel.
-Jang was your brother.
What's the difference?!
-Jang thinks for himself.
I'm not responsible.
-You're all alike.
You take everything from us,
and you give nothing.
I hate all of you!
-But, Sally, we were friends...
-Hi, I'm Johnny Longtorso.
Can I be of any help here?
-Leave me alone, please!
♪♪
-What's up, little actress.
-Uh, maybe this
isn't a good time,
but, uh, could you
launder my pants?
-No, Zenda.
I don't hate you,
but...[Sighs]
-But you wish you'd never
heard of Centaurus --
or me.
-I didn't say that.
-Uh, let's just say
that I don't hate you.
I-I'm not gonna call you
for racquetball,
if that's what you mean.
♪♪
-I wonder what she wanted.
-Here's my card.
Johnny Longtorso.
-Here, Sally.
-It's PEZ.
Make you feel better.
-It'll kill the pain.
♪♪
-And, uh, here --
It's my motorman's helper.
-Finish it!
-I wish I could do more.
I wish I were a doctor.
-I wish I were a pixie,
but let's get real.
-You wished for her,
and you got her.
-What did I get?
Nothing.
Well, I'm gonna try wishing!
I wish I were dead!
-That could be arranged.
-We're gonna be alright.
Admiral King will
come back for us.
Cosmos I'sprobably on its way
here this very minute.
-And hey, you got a sling
out of the deal,
and it's a pretty neat one.
-Even if they know where we are,
Command Headquarters
will never let him turn back.
-We're too annoying for anyone
to consider picking us up.
It's over.
-I know Admiral King, too.
Anyway,
we've got to hope, Sally.
♪♪
-Nice speech.
Now can I get some sleep,
for goodness sake?
-Nice statue.
Oh! She's real.
-Weren't you in Valley High
or Hawaiian High?
-You'd better get some rest,
Zenda.
We may have a long way to go
before we get out
of this jungle.
-Do you really believe
they'll be back to look for us?
-Of course I do.
-You're a good man, Charles.
-Brown.
-Your faith and courage
even in defeat.
-And my feet hurt like hell
right now.
Ba-da-boom.
-We're still alive.
♪♪
-Tomorrow, we should be able
to reach the foothills.
It'll be safer there.
-If I read my script correctly,
that is.
-...we can still
live on this planet...
if we just trust each other.
♪♪
-We could play booblie-ooblie
for years.
And the banana will stick.
-Oh, we better get outta here.
-Alright.
-Wonder what she wanted.
♪♪
[Door creaks]
[Whirring]
[Clanging]
-Joel! This is your life!
[Applause effect]
You're an ambitious young man
who began your life in space
as a custodian
for Gizmonic Institute.
Do you remember this voice?
-There's an unidentified
satellite straying
into our orbital path!
-Oh, well, that's easy.
It's, uh, my old friend Crow.
I think he's talking
about the time we partied
with the fellas from Salyut 7.
-Uh! Uh! Joel!
Joel, help!
Big satellite!
Big death!
Danger, wreckage,
ouch, sting, pain.
Hey, where did this couch
come from, anyway?
-Uh, I-I found it
in one of the crates
down in the loading bay.
I thought I'd redecorate.
What's this about
a death satellite?
-Oh, yeah. Uh...big --
big death satellite.
Oh, big! Pain.
Look, run.
Help, help.
-Hey, just settle down.
Come up here.
Come on up here and sit down.
Tell me all about it, okay?
Just take a few deep breaths.
That's alright.
-Well, there's, uh...
a big satellite out there
and, uh, we're gonna
collide with it, and...
-What?!
-Oh!
[Cans clatter]
-Oh, Cambot,
give me an exterior
of the ship, quick!
Jeepers.
-What's going on?!
-Get behind the couch, you two.
The redcoats are coming.
Alright, little death satellite,
Joely's got the exo-pinchers on,and he's nobody's sweetheart.
You and me going
round and round,
mano a mano.
Here comes lunch.
Give me the exo.
That's right,
little doomsday machine,
come to papa.
Feel my steel.
Now to bring it inside.
Cambot,
give me the interior shot.
-Do you have to bring
everything you find in space
into the living room?
-Sure looks like a
doomsday device, alright.
Uh, Joel,
are we up a creek, here?
-It's a doomsday machine
alright,
and I think I actually activated
its self-destruct mechanism.
I'd say we have roughly an hour
to disarm this thing.
[Machine chimes]
-Correction --
You have an hour and 37 minutes
to disarm,
and yes, you are up a creek.
-Oh, golly.
And we got commercial sign
on top of everything!
♪♪
[Insects chirping]
-We gotta disarm that
satellite, you two.
This is serious.
-Going down for the count.
♪♪
-That was no boating accident.
-I'm sorry I had
to kill you, Dave,
but you understand,
I couldn't let you live.
You see, you knew too much!
♪♪
-It's the Green Hornet.
-Que tal?
♪♪
-[Whistles]
-You'd think in the future,
they'd be able
to get hip waders.
♪♪
-Oh, very sneaky.
-He's trying to sneak
across the rice paper.
♪♪
-If only I could get
to my utility belt!
Ugh!
♪♪
-Smooth.
-I'll take that, Mr. Bond.
-What are you trying to do?
-Someone is out there.
-Who could be out there?
Huh?!
♪♪
-Take that, Mr. Bono.
That's to you, Confucius.
♪♪
-Bring...the...car...around...
-[Shouts indistinctly]
-...general.
-Do not take us back!
♪♪
-Strange way for lodge brothers
to greet each other.
-Don't just do something!
Stand there!
-Oh, a neck massage.
-Tiny...bubbles...
in my...larynx.
[Gagging]
♪♪
-I'm not on either side.
Ooh, sorry!
♪♪
-Kill your brother.
It's the only way to reinforce
the director's
white male reality.
♪♪
Take the shot.
Come on!
♪♪
-Help!
-Mom...always...
did like you...best.
♪♪
-Gee, I --
I missed.
♪♪
-Well, I know you just
shot your brother,
but why don't you
just come over here
and love me a little bit.
Yeah.
-[Sobbing]
Love me.
Love me!
♪♪
-Meanwhile at the ocarina.
-10,000 miles, sir.
Velocity now 5 miles per second.
-Alright, Allen.
Set gravitation compensators
for an altitude of 50 miles.
Decelerate to zero velocity.
-GC 50 miles.
Zero velocity.
♪♪
-500.
-500 what?
-Stand by emergency.
-300.
-What?!
-200.
-Stop teasing me.
-150.
100.
-Sold.
-75.
60.
55.
50.
-And so on and so on.
Stationary orbit, sir.
-50 miles and locked in, sir.
-Very good, Mr. Scott.
-Told you he'd like it.
-Oh, picture, picture.
-...would you join me on
the observation deck, please.
-He asked me!
He asked me!
-Just let me slip
my dance belt on.
-So, we've finally arrived.
-Did you have any doubt,
Captain?
-About reaching Solaris? No.
-Let's see.
Looks like a hairline fracture.
-...still alive, Dr. Farrell?
-Well, there's always a chance.
-Not a very good chance,
I believe.
-Oh, what do you know?
-[Sighs] Yes, the facts
do indicate that this planet
has an unpleasant environment,
but not necessarily hostile.
It has a carbon-water
oxygen system.
-Sounds kinda like a Slurpee.
-[Speaks native language]
-Huh?
-Jung has calculated that
for the past three months
while we've been traveling,
18 years have gone by
on the planet.
-That means it'll be legal
to date my girlfriend now.
My CD should be rolling over
just about now.
-I believe our admiral
will not give up
until he has definitely proved
there are no survivors.
-He's gonna get sleeves someday.
-It'll probably
cost him his command.
-Once, there was such leaders
on Centaurus.
-The admiral has his way,
there will be again.
He's determined to prove
that Centaurus
can rebuild its culture.
-What a kiss-up.
-...this is so, Doctor?
-Well, I'd say that Linda
is a brilliant example
of what can be done.
-Through bizarre
experimentation.
-When she was removed
to the colony,
the others were not.
-What are you trying
to tell me, Jung?
-I abhor you, round eye,
and all your ways.
-...a people will
change their ways
only if they wish to do so.
A man may be removed from...
-Uh, wait, wait.
Let me get a pencil here.
-But it is difficult to
remove the land from the man.
-All: And you can't remove
the land from the man,
the chalice from the palace,
and the brew that is true.
-The flagon with the dragon
has the pellet with the poison.
♪♪
-It's such a beautiful planet.
-Hey, settle down.
It's just a painting.
-...Centaurus.
So green and peaceful.
-It may not be so peaceful
down there.
-Yeah, the grass
is always greener
on the other side of the galaxy.
-We can't trust young planets.
-What do you mean, Admiral?
-They're lazy,
and they listen to loud music.
-...living things
completely unknown to us.
-Hasn't this planet
ever been explored?
-Not according to
our galactic records.
-But, uh...
then I couldn't read 'em,
'cause I spilled coffee on 'em.
-No sign of life of any kind,
Admiral --
human or otherwise.
-The creatures on these planets
are deceiving.
Feet on the ground,
you can't always trust
what you see.
-Bill, how do you
fight your panty lines?
-Huh? Oh, that's man talk.
We'll never understand it.
-18 years is a long time.
-And they couldn't have
picked a worse place to crash.
-Hey says that like
there's a good place to crash.
-Certainly
a botanist's paradise.
-I hate to tell you this, Phil,
but all your aquarium fish
are dead.
-...comparable to our bison
about 5 million years ago.
-Doc, uh...
...could man exist...
in that environment?
-Probably.
-Let's all speak in...
broken sentences.
-I think it would be mostly
combating the elements,
defending himself from...
who knows what.
There could be some
rather ferocious beasts
roaming about that terrain.
-Are the scenes just as static
down on the planet, Bill?
-...to Command Headquarters.
Inform them we're going to
make a landing on this planet.
-And use the good stationery.
-Yep.
-That deep canyon.
-Uh-huh.
-Beyond the jungle.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah, I see it.
-That's your landing site.
-Oh.
-You mean it?
-Sergeant Allen.
-Yep.
-Landing stations.
-Gotcha.
-Yes, sir.
-Who should I tell
these orders to?
-Attention all personnel,
attention all personnel --
landing stations.
-Stand by gravitators.
-Maneuvering room,
stand by gravitators.
-Gotcha.
-Maneuvering room ready
and standing by.
-Thanks, angel.
-Hate to say it, Lieutenant,
but I got a feeling
the old man's got
a bad case of cosmic fever.
-Well, I've got some salve
in my foot locker.
-...spirit of adventure, Chief?
I thought you loved this life.
-Spirit I've got,
adventure I've had,
love I was looking forward to.
-I know what you mean, Chief.
Remember the words of that
great planetary prophet.
-Yeah, what'd he say?
-He said, "Let them
that don't want none
have memories of..."
Forget it.
-[Laughs]
-Great proverb.
Hope you didn't get any of that
tattooed anyplace important.
-Bzzz!
-Hey, I see a spot.
Let's pull up over there.
-Bzzz.
♪♪
-Alright, let's take a break.
Go easy on the water.
-It eliminates rest stops.
-Everyone take one
oxygenian tablet.
No more.
-I didn't say Simon Says.
-Like breathing under water.
-Hot water.
-We'll get used to it.
-It's like being
in the crews' quarters.
-Imagine having to live
in an inferno like this.
-Probably not too bad
up in the highlands.
-This planet's not
too unlike Centauria.
-Aside from the fact that
it's completely different.
-I imagine the Centaurians could
adapt to this planet
very easily.
-With all this vegetation?
Naw, they like the deserts, Doc.
You give them barren,
windswept oceans of sand.
-All: Shut up!
-Say, Doc...
-Do you think
I'll be offed first?
-Uh, I mean Mr. Farrell.
Old Jung said that
in the three months
it took us
to get back to this planet,
18 years passed by here.
How does he figure that?
-He was kidding.-...told you half a dozen times.
It's the time paradox.
What's a'matter with you?
-O-Oh, yeah, I, uh --
I missed that day.
Sorry.
-...I still don't see it.
-It's a matter of reference...
-Uh, it's too complicated
for you, bonehead.
-...traveling at one speed.
This planet travels at another.
-You get it, kid?
For three months,
we've been barreling along
at nearly speed of light.
-Yeah, yeah.
I-I know that.
But I-I --
-Look. Look.
This planet rotates on its axis
at only 1,000 miles an hour.
Now, that speed determines
the length of the day,
the month, and the year here.
-We getting through?
-Why don't you come up
to my room tonight,
and I'll explain it to ya.
-Oh, look, uh, at the speed
we were traveling in space
for three months,
that was the equivalent
of six thousand, five hundred --
-La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la!
Can't hear you!
-La, la, la, la!
-Yeah, sure.
It's simple.
It's, uh --
It's just a matter
of reference points.
Anybody can see that.
-He's bluffing.
-He's a twit.
-See anything?
-A few birds.
Nothing else.
-What'd he expect to see,
a welcoming committee?
-Don't get funny.
-Don't worry.
He won't.
-Hey.
You hear something, Chief?
-I don't think
it's a welcoming committee.
-Like something walking around
over there.
-Something big.
-[Growls]
-Don't anybody move.
-Oh, my God.
-It's an insert shot
of an iguana!
-Their technology must be
light years ahead of ours!
Their use of stock footage
is amazing!
♪♪
-Oh, great.
That's your answer
to everything.
-How do you like
your lizard done, boys?
-I never knew lizards
were so darn flammable.
-No thunder lizards were hurtduring the filming of this film.
-Mmm! Extra "cripsy."
-"Cripsy?"
-Yeah.
-You alright, Allen?
-Sure. Can I go change now?
-Yeah, yeah.
I think --
-I soiled myself.
-What is it, Allen?
-I c--
I can't find my heartbeat!
-[Laughs]
Nothing like a little adventure,eh, Lieutenant?
-Try lower.
-Set up a beamer here.
-BMW?
-Cosmos I,this is Scott.
Do you receive me?
-Gutless 1,we read you.
-...receiving you, Commander.
Stevens standing by.
-Ensign, inform the admiral
that I advise no one be allowed
to leave the ship
without being well armed.
-Scott, this is King.
-Are you speaking
into a Waterpik?
-Well, we've encountered one
of those deceptive creatures
you mentioned.
A giant lizard.
It's been destroyed,
but I'm sure
there are others in this area.
We're about halfway to
the crash site now, Admiral.
I'll leave a beamer
at this location.
That's all, sir.
-Very well, Mr. Scott.
Carry on.
Keep a sharp watch.
Don't want to be caught
with your guard down.
-Yes, sir.
-"Very well, Mr. Scott.
Carry on.
Keep a sharp watch.
You don't want to be caught
with your guard down."
-Stop doing a Cagney impression.
It's not that great.
-My commanding officer
asked for volunteers
for an important expedition.
I thought he meant exhibition.
-Yeah, and my uncle's
the producer in the film, too.
-Alright, men, let's move.
And keep a sharp watch.
-It's our first Christmas
on the planet,
and you've been just grand.
♪♪
We better go be
with the others now.
-If that the way
they grow lizards around here,
I'd hate to run into a snake.
-[Chuckles]
-Good one.
-There's a well on this ship.
-What?!
-Sorry, men,
your liberty's canceled.
No one is to leave this ship
under any circumstances.
-Have they located
the Cosmos III,sir?
-Not yet.
-Ah, well, there goes
the ball game, huh?
-They must've run
into trouble out there.
-Well, I wish I was with them.
Anything'd be better
than being stuck in this
king-sized community capsule.
-Oh, you...
-Admiral King.
Linda is out of the ship.
-Are you sure?
-She said she wished
to breathe the fresh air,
to feel the warm of the sun.
-Just tell me where she went,
Hemingway, come on.
-...your permission.
-She's been dying to get off
this ship ever since we landed.
-Will it help
if I strike a pose right here?
♪♪
-Harris, get my field gear.
-And my stirrup pants.
-Tell him that we'll be --
-Admiral King.
You can't take this chance, sir.
If anything should happen to youor -- or Commander Scott...
-Yes, yes, you'd be in charge.
Yes, I realize that.
-Harris,
you and Wilson go look for her.
She's probably near the ship.
-Yes, sir.
-Bring laser rifles with you.
-I'll stay here
and take more lithium.
-Yes, sir.
-Don't worry, Admiral.
We'll find her.
-Spin and Marty to the rescue!
-Poor Linda.
She's such a lost child.
-Karen...
anything happens to her, I...
I'll never forgive myself.
-I understand.
-She's just like her mother.
-Oh, Ward.
The beaver turned out okay.
-...curious,
filled with childlike dreams
of another world.
-What is she,
Anne of Green Gables,
all the sudden?
Hey!
-...cannot be changed.
-What did he want?
-Oops.
-I didn't know
he knew Linda's mother.
I thought she was killed
in the Centaurians travel war.
-It is true,
but Admiral knew her
long before that.
He made many expedition
into the desert in those years.
-Ah, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
You're describing
the plot of "Kung Fu."
-Who was Linda's father?
-We better get outta here.
-Yeah, you're right.
-Oh, boy.-We gotta disarm that satellite!
Oh, yeah, I want to help!
-Let's get going.
♪♪
-You know,
this makes no sense at all.
Whoever heard of
a doomsday machine
with a fold-lock top in it.
-Hey, hey, Joel. Look.
I found an instruction manual
right there, see.
-Thanks.
It says, "Isaac Asimov's
Literary Doomsday Machine."
It's an instruction manual.
It must be over
1,000 pages long.
How typical.
-Literary Doomsday?
Isn't that when
your library fines
exceed the price of the book?
-Uh, I thought it was, uh...
every time Jackie Collins
makes it
to the best-seller list.
-Ah, settle down, you goonheads.
We got this doomsday machine
to disarm and, well,
we gotta check the manual.
Let's see.
It looks like it's translated
from the Korean or something.
-They must have, uh...
subcontracted the satellite
for 'em.
-Uh, I don't --
I don't get it.
Asimov must've gone mad.
Why would anyone want
to make a doomsday machine?
-Well, he's probably mad
'cause no one else
is as smart as him,
or else that L. Ron Hubbard
has more followers than him.
-Well, didn't Asimov
try to establish
the Church of the Super Quiz
once?
-Oh, knock it off,
you spinach shins.
I gotta read this manual.
"Step one --
It will be very enjoyable
for you to separate
the ocular filter coupling
of from the decapaciter,
which is stout
and yellow sometimes."
Crow, you better scan this
and give me the instructions.
-[Whirring]
Got it.
-Brother.
Okay.
"Most very kindly, uh...
find the lookee switch,
which is nice
and sitting there
with green label
that leaves you singing."
-I think I got it.
-Okay.
"Carefully disregard
and do not do
the very wrong thing
or much confusion
will result..."
Tell me about it.
"...with sparks, flowers,
and loud report on some models.
Glue Batman to CG --
detail omitted for clarity?"
This is really confusing.
-Who wrote this --
Charlie Callas?
-Hey, oh, oh.
Wait, there's more.
Uh, uh, it says, uh...
"Clip, uh, red wire
likes you best
with firm hand and glad heart."
-Okay.
I think that outta do it.
-"But first...
clip the blue wire.
Got you, scrawny man."
-[Laughs]
[Alarm blaring]
Well, that's what it said.
-Oh, man, we got movies.
[All screaming]
[Whirring]
[Door creaks]
♪♪
-Oh, my eyes.
-You got creamed.
You okay?
♪♪
-Say...
-[Screams]
-Seems like a nice lookin' gal!
-Are you chaffing like a bear?
Or is it just me?
-It sounded like
a bird call to me.
-Sounded like a girl
screaming at a snake.
-Come on.
Linda's in trouble.
♪♪
-Hey, the snake pushed
her into the river.
-Fortunately, I have
my Johnny Rocket crossbow.
♪♪
-Snake on a stick.
-Hey, look what
someone threw back.
Cool. This'll look great
over the mantle.
I can't believe it.
This is a keeper.
♪♪
-Hey, watch those hands.
-Amazing what you find
if you just look.
♪♪
-She'll be perfect
for my experiments.
-And Quincey will
be so proud of me.
♪♪
-Say...
this hotel's got everything.
Wonder where the game room is.
♪♪
-Ah.
Get a load of this place,
will ya.
It's a regular paradise island.
-I hear you, man.
-It's also the end of the trail,
unless you're a mountain goat.
-Oh, I used to be.
-...she climbed up there.
I think we missed her.
Maybe she's back
there someplace.
-Wait a minute.
♪♪
Tracks.
She's been right
around here someplace.
-Like right where
these tracks were made?
-D-Do you think she fell in?
I mean,
do the Centaurians
know how to swim?
♪♪
-I don't know.
Her boot!
-Dibs, dibs.
-Das boot.
-Let me drink champagne
out of it, just to be sure.
♪♪
-Look at the size of that thing.
-Oh, I've seen trees
bigger than that.
That's nothing.
-Let's get back to the ship.
Let's go.
Come on, come on, come on.
♪♪
-We've been pacing
this studio for hours.
When do we get
some action happening?
♪♪
-Hmm, coconut cream pie,
car made out of bamboo,
and a sailor's hat.
What's it all mean?
♪♪
-Alright.
Let's take five.
-1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
[Laughs] Psych!
♪♪
-What's a'matter, Bradley?
This hike too much for ya?
-Oh, no, Doc, I always
enjoy a 40-mile walk
on a lovely day like this.
-You ever see the movie
"Alive," doughnut boy?
-...you were 10 pounds
overweight.
-Are you kiddin', Doc?
I've been on a diet
for seven days,
and so far,
all I've lost is a week.
-Good one.
-And your self-respect
for that joke.
-Yeah.
That's the story of my life.
I'm always volunteering
for something.
I remember one day,
back in headquarters,
I volunteered
for a karate course.
They taught me all the chops
to the head, the neck,
the shoulders, the stomach --
the whole thing there.
Karate kicks -- hey!
-Now, who are you?
Donald O'Connor?
-Hi-keeba! Ha!
-You know,
I could watch that all day.
Do that again, will ya.
-And after
completing the course,
I became a karate expert.
-When did he become an idiot?
-I went around breaking boards
with my bare hand.
The first time
I saluted Admiral King,
I almost knocked my brains out.
-Sure you didn't succeed?
-I had to volunteer for this,
this mission to Centaurus,
and look where it got us.
-This guy's a hoot.
-Well, like you always told me,
Lieutenant, where's
your spirit of adventure?
-I left it in my other pants.
-That's what makes all
of this worthwhile --
the adventure...
day after day,
week after week,
month after month,
year after year.
All the sheer thrill
of it all --
perusing the planets,
unifying the universe,
galloping through the galactics.
-All: Shut up!
-...we had to the planet Gage
if I live to be normal.
We landed our ship in the middle
of the densest part
of the jungle,
and we were about 200 yards
from the ship when...
-Morty Gunty appearing this week
at the Blaine Community Theater
in Shakespeare's "King Lear."
-...from head to toe,
with fire and flame shooting
out of all three nostrils.
Well, I raised my laser gun...
-Shut him up.
-...activating mechanism.
The gun wouldn't work.
-I can't shut him up.
-It looked like certain
death for all of us.
-I can't reach his mouth.
-I reached back, and I grabbed
a handful of yours,
and I threw it right in
the beast's face and killed it.
-Now just a minute, Bradley.
You reached back
and grabbed a handful of what?
-Yours.
A handful of yours.
And I threw it right in --
-O-Okay. Okay, Bradley,
Tell me, what's yours?
-Uh, I'll have
a three-day pass, sir --
-Ba-boom!
-I'll kill him!
-Ba-ba-boom!
-I shouldn't have asked.
-[Laughs]
-Let's move out, shall we?
-Uh, he'll be
riding in the trunk
on the way back to Earth.
-He's a real child of hell.
♪♪
-I gotta get a new log out here
or somethin'.
[Monkey chitters]
♪♪
-Ah, Wilma, you're up.
-Have you met Steve, my monkey?
♪♪
-Well, you got
some flaking there,
and you could use a henna.
-Pretty girl.
-Wh-Who are you?
-I am Tang.
-I'm not just
for breakfast anymore.
-That's my favorite drink!
-It's short for
Australopithecus africanus.
-I am Centaurian.
-Tang is my favorite drink.
-You are Centaurian.
We are same.
♪♪
-Well, how did you get here?
On this planet?
-It is my homeland.
♪♪
-You were born here?
Your mother was aboard
the Cosmos III.
-And your mother swimmed
after troop ships, lady.
-Survivors?
-Yes.
Your mother and father.
Where are they?
-Um, you're wearing them.
♪♪
-I will take you to them.
-Uh, Tang...
-Uh, fresh out.
But I've got Catawba juice.
-Clothes wet.
You fall in water.
-Oh, yes, I remember.
There was a serpent.
-I kill serpent.
-Here, eat this hot stick.
You'll like it.
♪♪
-Leave the shower curtain here.
-Oh, by the way,
I did that totem pole
just 'cause I thought
I was supposed to.
♪♪
-How much per month for this...
with the damage deposit?
♪♪
-[Speaking indistinctly]
-Gong.
♪♪
-Now join me
in my dance of death.
♪♪
-That's cold.
-It is Zenda.
She's beautiful.
-Mother.
-She's not bad,
except for a little freezer burnaround the edges.
-It's Clarence Birdseye.
-That is Lieutenant Anderson!
He's not a Centaurian.
-My father.
-Well, they're now
a bowling trophy.
I must tell the admiral
about this.
I must go back to the ship
that brought me here.
Do you know where the ship is,
Tang?
-I know.
I take you there.
-And then I'll get
some pronouns.
♪♪
[Water bubbling]
-Meanwhile,
back at the dry ice pool...
♪♪
-[Sighs]
What a smell!
-Smell?
-Oh, that's just me.
-Bottle that muck,
you have a great secret weapon.
-Yeah, they could
use it for deodorant.
You rub it on,
the smell stays,
but you disappear.
-Good one.
-It's boiling crude oil,
Commander.
-Boy, what a spot
for a steam bath.
-Just cross the log,
and you're in the club.
-Hand me the rope.
♪♪
-You could walk around.
-Too easy.
Sure glad the prop boys laid
this log out here for us.
♪♪
-If the Wallendas can do it,
we can do it.
-...more nerve
than I thought he had.
-Scott's a good man, Bradley.
-He has wonderful
bone structure,
great teeth,
and a darling figure.
-Yeah, but what
a miserable place
to have to search in.
-Sir, he's right over there.
-A hazardous mission
is like the mirror of truth.
When you face it,
you see your true self.
-Oh, shut up.
What are you, Confucius?
Just cross the dry ice
and shut up!
-Why don't you build
a better bridge?
-Wrong kind of engineers.
-Uh, you see, uh...
we just play with toy trains.
-Frankly, yeah.
-Doc, I don't think
Allen better try it.
-Might want to take the slack
out of that rope.
-Allen, you stay behind.
-You little panty-waist boy.
If that was my kid,
I'd whack him!
-I'm okay, Doc. If, uh --
If you can make it, I can.
-Suit yourself.
-He's got it secure.
Let's go.
-He's got tequila?
♪♪
-Easy.
-My blood pressure
is just racing.
-Why don't they just
go around right there?
-I'm coming too, Chief!
-Wait, Allen!
Don't follow so close!
-Don't fall.
Don't fall.
-Jinx! Jinx!
-[Indistinct shouting]
-Jinx.
-Don't fall.
Don't fall.
-[Trills tongue]
-Miss.
-Chicken chicken.
-[Screams]
-Ooh, shame.
What a pity.
-Help!
-Hot foot.
-It's gainer.
-Yes, it is.
-Well, I guess
he's not in the club.
-Never did like him anyway.
-That's right.
Lousy.
That's what
this whole mission is.
-Can I have his locker?
-Lousy.
What the hell are
we trying to prove, anyway?
Searching a stinkin'
nowhere planet
for a bunch of survivors
that may not exist?
-Hey, I got Angelo to think of.
-Take it easy, Chief.
-Take it easy?
You watch a man die like that,
and you say, "Take it easy?"
-Hey, I thought it was funny.
Why?
-[Gasps]
-You alright now, Chief?
-Yeah.
Thanks for not hitting me.
-Sorry, sir.
Something just happened to me.
Got a little shook, I guess.
-Forget it, Chief.
We're all a little shook.
-Dickweed.
-Now, we're almost there.
Let's move on.
-Dork.
♪♪
-Come on, son.
-I know how you're feeling.
You see this shoulder?
It's here if you need it.
Idiot.
-Now, would you go back across
the log and unhook the rope?
-That makes me hungry.
-Is he primordial soup yet?
♪♪
-Now, where did we park?
-More of the same.
Oh, brother.
♪♪
-Who's line is it?
-Somebody.
♪♪
-Someone's gotta have a line.
There we are.
-Kinda sickening, isn't it?
Nobody could've survived
this crash.
-Bradley,
you and the chief wait here.
We can't be sure
what we might find inside.
With me, Doc?
-Yeah, you two disposable
characters wait here.
♪♪
-Wow.
Looks like they turned
that ship into a restaurant.
I love these fern bars.
Looks like
an interstellar Denny's.
It's great.
-Wow. They had
more switches than we do.
♪♪
-Did you float an air biscuit
or is that me?
♪♪
-Captain Ross.
-Hey, their doggy left
all their bones here.
-That's the people, you dolt.
-Oh.
♪♪
-Nice wallet.
-That's his sternum.
Don't touch it.
-That we know of.
-[Barks]
-I want to check every
compartment in this ship.
Ask Bradley and the chief
to do it.
Get 'em back here.
♪♪
-Huh.
-It says, "Thou shalt not k--"
-That was in the other show.
-Oh, yeah.
-It's a closin' play.
♪♪
-And says, "Ahab was obsessed
with the great white one."
♪♪
It's a well! There's
a little girl down there!
-Well, it's the same situation
down in the maneuvering room.
The entire engineering crew.
-The maneuvering room?
Don't you mean the bathroom?
-It's like a tomb.
-You know, there's one thing
that puzzles me, Doc.
-Fractions.-...hatch is left standing open.
-Huh?
-And, uh, looks likesome of them have been forced...
-Kinda like
your characterization.
-So someone else has
searched through the ship?
-Yeah, something like that.
-We've accounted for all
but five.
-There were five survivors.
-You mean that recorder
still works after 18 years?
-Yeah, but it's on an 8-track.
-Emergency power pack is as goodas the day it was installed.
Listen to this.
-And now there are
only three of us,
and I don't expect
Sergeant Long to last
more than a few days now.
-Long won't last long.
-...caused a loss of sight
in both eyes,
and his brain seems
to have been damaged somehow.
I'm also certain that my fever
will soon overcome me.
There are no more drugs
aboard the ship.
-This planet's totally dry,
dudes.
Don't look to be
scorin' nothin' here.
-Year 1, 74th day.
[Recorder clicks]
-That's the last report?
-74 long days...
watching the sky...
waiting for us.
Waiting for death.
-Nice speech, Jim.
-Anderson knew it would
take us 18 years to get back.
The important thing is,
he knew we would.
-Thank God we did.
-You think they might be alive
up in the mountains?
-It's possible.
-[Screaming]
-Jim's constipated.
-[Screaming continues]
-Hey, Chief, what's wrong?
-[Screams]
-What's wrong with him, Doc?
-I don't know.
-Why don't you ask him?
♪♪
-Quick, get back!
-Oh, my God, how horrible,
to be killed by a plush toy!
-Tarantula.
Don't make any quick moves.
Doc, keep perfectly still.
Can I have your laser gun.
-Yes, sir.
-Kinda late now, isn't it?
♪♪
-Careful, Scott, he sees you.
He can spring that far.
-We rigged him that way.
-Look out!
He's gonna jump.
[High-pitched whining]
-Nice ricochet sound.
-The hopping spider of Rylos 4.
-Well, I guess
he's really an angel now.
-Yep.
-He died more from shock
than the poison.
-Little leech, I guess.
-Quick diagnosis, though.
-Let's go.
-Well, don't
everybody be so sad.
♪♪
-What else is on the tape?
-Uh, Eddie Money,
"Two Tickets to Paradise."
That's about it.
And the DeFranco Family.
I don't think you'd like it.
-Two of them did.
They murdered Ross.
-This'll hit the admiral
pretty hard.
-Yeah.
-Hit them pretty hard, too, Doc.
-Wrecked 'em?
Damn near killed 'em.
-And so, Johnny Longtorso
and his industrial band
of bad-boy spacefaring pals
step out into the cold air
of Central Park.
♪♪
-Oh...
-Ahhhhh!
-They were your mothers'.
-Well, they were
my mother's shower curtains.
-Oh, yes, Tang.
-Crazy woman.
I offer her something
to drink --
She thinks it's my name
all of the sudden.
-What the...?
♪♪
-How long have your mother
and father been gone, Tang?
-You mean...frozen?
-I was child.
-Then who taught you to speak?
How'd you live?
-Mother teach.
She live until...
-She held me back
in the third grade.
♪♪
-Do you live here all alone?
-Yes.
Alone.
-If you don't count
my 27 monkeys.
-...people on this planet?
-Yes, there are others.
Savages who hate and kill.
They do not want Tang
to live in their country.
-Oh, you mean Crash Orange,
Goofy Grape, Lefty Lemon?
That whole gang?
-Only enemies.
-But there is room
for many people to live here.
Why should they object?
-Well, this is
the high-rent district,
and you know how people get.
They are primitive men.
-The producers?
-No, these men are different.
-Oh, the executive producers.
-Natch.
-...fear men who are different.
♪♪
-Oh, wow!
Mom never looked thatgood.
-Beautiful...
girl.
♪♪
-My name is Linda.
-My name is Lucky.
-Linda.
Tang.
-I'm not just for breakfast
anymore.
-Can I call you...
Ovaltine?
-I'll drink to that.
-Who undressed me?
-[Grunts]
-Linda's clothes wet.
I undress.
♪♪
-Nice tag, Tang.
-I did not mean to hurt you.
♪♪
-I can love only through pain.
-Do not be afraid of me.
♪♪
-I am not afraid of you, Tang.
-Bang-shangalang, Tang.
-Wang, bang, thank you, Tang.
♪♪
[Thunder crashes]
-♪ The weather started
getting rough ♪
♪ And Tang and she were tossed
-Zzz-z-z-z!
[Thunder crashes]
-Dean will get, uh,
lady and the plumbers
to do all the dirty work.
-Lieutenant Anderson,
navigation officer, Cosmos III.
-Hey, Crow, sounds like one
of the more boring episodes
of "Prairie Home Companion,"
huh?
-Yeah, let's get it on tape.
[Thunder crashes]
-Canyon's to the west.
That would place himin the upper end of this canyon.
Probably a cave
high in the cliffs.
Well, they'd be fairly safe
from the --
-I know what you mean!
-Admiral.
Do you seriously believe
any of them are still alive?
-Maybe I do. I don't know
what I think of that.
-Well, then, why haven't
they used the radio?
Or continue the tape report
beyond 74 days?
-He has a point, Admiral.
-Granted, but...
even if we find nothing --
-[Shouts in gibberish]
Talk like this, mm.
-...at least we'd be sure.
-Admiral King.
Are the dead worth more lives
than the living?
-What's a dead man
other than a live man
without any life?
-Sergeant Allen, the Chief...
Linda...
-I'm not convinced
that Linda is dead, either.
-[Grunting, mumbling]
-Might possibly be a captive.
-A captive?
-Harris and Wilson
said the serpent
was killed by a metal shaft...
possibly an arrow.
[Thunder crashes]
There might be primitive men
on this planet.
-"Men without pocket squares."
-Hey, did you just get back
from the dentist or something?
-Forewarning -- I'm going
to go out and find out.
-Uh...
-Did he just get
a shot of Novocain?
-JD.
-Goodnight, gentlemen.
[Thunder crashes]
-[Exhales sharply]
Is it my breath?
[Thunder crashes]
-Oh, Cap'n Crunch comfort ring,
help me out
of this awful jam now.
-Shazam!
♪♪
[Upbeat music plays]
-Yeah.
♪♪
-Go, Annette, go.
-How'd she get
that X-ray machine
to sound that good?
-The space samba.
♪♪
-Wow. She'd be perfect
for your experiments.
♪♪
-A little girl
is trapped down there,
and all you can do is dance.
It was murder.
-Ah, the sexual harassment laws
are a lot looser in the future.
-You know you love it.
-Yeah, but, uh, not when
we can't do anything about it.
-Six inches. Come on.
-Alright, break it up.
Mr. Bradley,
didn't you ever read
the regulations covering
shipboard romances?
-'Course I did,
but [laughs]
this started a long time
before we came aboard.
-I can only read braille.
-...get back home,
or you'll find yourself
with a busted ensign.
-A busted ensign.
We all know how painful
that can be.
-...on a sweet little
junior officer like this
just 'cause you're jealous?
-Bradley, there are some men whocan send me right into orbit.
You couldn't even get me
onto the launching pad.
-Yikes.
Nice tag.
-Mr. Scott!
-Oh, you're over there.
I didn't look.
-Why isn't my field gear ready?
Bradley!
-Yes, sir?
-Where's Mr. Scott?
Why isn't the search party
ready to leave?
-Mr. Scott...
-[Speaks gibberish]
-...Doc and Harris with him.
He -- He said you wouldn't
let anybody else go.
-Hmm.
He -- He said that, did he?
-I knew that.
-But those were your orders,
weren't they, Admiral?
-Yes.
-Hmm.
-Yes, of course.
Hmm.
-Has he reported in yet?
-[Speaks gibberish]
-He said he would investigate
the waterfall area,
and then report to you.
-Well, now...
let me know the moment
you hear from him.
-Thank you, Betty,
Veronica, Jughead.
-Hey, you know something?
He didn't tell Scott to go.
He was gonna go himself.
-Yes, I know.
Commander told me about it
last night.
-He was very high.
♪♪
-Man, we've been walking around
this studio for months.
-We've gone too far.
We're on the Indian set now.
Turn back.
-We searched
this area thoroughly.
She isn't here, Admiral.
We're gonna head
for the cliffs now.
I'll let you know
if we find anything.
Yes, sir.
-But your bath is ready, sir.
-Doc...
what kind of metal
would you say this is?
-Some kind of steel alloy?
-Wrong.
But thanks for playing.
-What are you driving at?
-Well, there's only
one kind of device
that shoots an arrow like this.
-Uh, a bow?
-A crossbow.
Maybe a Centaurian crossbow.
-Maybe.
-Doc, we may be
on the very trail
of the man...
who murdered Captain Ross.
-Let's go check out
the cave set, you schlugs.
♪♪
-Hello, world.
-It's Peter Pan and Wendy.
-Hey, get me!
I'm a wood nymph!
-My name isn't Tang.
It's Puck.
Oh, I meant to do my work today,
but the wildflowers beckoned.
What could I do
but answer their call,
sweetly called
by the stringed lute,
and I came.
-Hmm?
-That was beautiful.
-Yes.
-I remember this place, Tang.
So lovely here, so peaceful.
-This all flows from
the other huts upstream.
-Here, I find Linda.
♪♪
-Come. We must eat.
-I don't know if we wanna
watch this next part.
-Uh, I kinda do.
-No, you better --
-Oh, come on.
[Doors thud and creak]
[Doors whir]
[Doors thud and clank]
No, it's the green wire, Joel.
Definitely the green.
-Look, who's holding
the screwdriver here, anyway?
-I give up. Who?
-Oh, that's enough
from the peanut gallery.
Thanks a lot, you two.
-Ah, heck, Joel.Go ahead and clip the blue wire.
It's just a doomsday machine.
If it goes up, it's not
like we're gonna be around
to experience oblivion.
-Well, by oblivion,
do you mean
experiential oblivion
or phenomenological oblivion?
-Hmm.
Interesting distinction.
Let's define our terms,
shall we?
-Well, Kierkegaard would
always say that --
-Listen, you screw-heads,
you better knock it off
or I'll brain you both
with my ball peen hammer.
Now, knock it off.
-Geez.
-Hmm. Interesting reaction toa logically defined supposition.
I think Camus would have, uh...
theorized differently on it.
-Oh, listen,
Mr. Smart-Aleck-Guy, what --
what wire would Camus cut?
-Well, uh, he'd cut
the blue one, I think,
and then if he was
still around after that,
he'd cut the green one.
-Eenie, meenie, miney, moe,
catch a robot by --
-Ah, the Samuel Beckett method.
-Uh, Joel, you're playing
dice with the universe.
I hope you realize that.
[Chiming]
-Welcome.
You have passed through
the first three thresholds
of the Isaac Asimov Literary
Satellite.
Answer the disarm code
or enjoy the consequences.
Remember, this and all literary
works of the last century
are the sole property
of Isaac Asimov
and his many affiliates.
Thank you for intruding.
You have five seconds.
-Oh, quick, Joel,
cut every wire.
-That's not gonna work.
It needs an access code.
-Oh, oh, try "ego."
-Ah, "sideburn."
-I'll try "I, Robot."
[Buzzing]
-I'm sorry.
The correct answer would
have been copyright.
You now have 6 nanoseconds
to realize the consequences.
[Indistinct talking]
-All: Huh?!
-This cockamamie satellite's
turned us all into
duplicate Isaac Asimovs.
-Hey, do you think
it's a conspiracy?
-Oh, no.
I, uh...
I covered the conspiracy topic
in my 10-volume
"History
of Assassinations and Coups."
-This is terrible, you guys.
-Oh, I don't know.
At least now I'll have
something to write about.
You know, I've been
thinking about annotating
the Manhattan phone directory.
-Oh, look, it's commercial sign.
That'll fit nicely
into my volume
on the effects of advertising
on the human psyche.
[Indistinct talking]
♪♪
-Oh.
[Indistinct talking]
-Shh!
-Oh.
-Watch the movie.
-I have never seen
such beautiful food.
On Centaurus,
at the colony and on my ship,
we have only
synthetic food to eat.
-I know.
Mother speak of this
before she leave on...
long journey beyond.
-She's in the cave, Tang.
Frozen.
-This much better food.
♪♪
-They're, uh...
Little Debbie cakes.
I, uh -- I gathered them
from the bear cave.
-They're fit for a king.
Here, king. Here, king.
Ba-boom. Zing.
-You have much to learn.
-Yeah, and they're
one-third less calories
than regular mangoes.
-You flunk third grade, though.
♪♪
-[Chuckles]
[Laughter]
-Ah, turn it around.
♪♪
No, the other way.
Oh, brother.
♪♪
-This Tiko, my hungry friend.
-Oh, he's still mad about
the whole evolution thing.
♪♪
-Let me show you how
to open these things.
Beautiful.
Look at this.
♪♪
-So, I grow a pelt
and crawl up on a rock?
♪♪
-Mm.
This is even better
than the other.
-The other what?
♪♪
-Can I have another banana,
Landslide?
-Come, Tiko.
Linda not hurt you.
She new friend.
-Come on.
Show her your red butt,
like at the zoo.
-Give Linda kiss.
-Mm. [Laughs]
-[Gasps] Oh.
-Here, Tiko.
-Nice babe you
got there, Tang.
♪♪
-Gotta go back
to my trainer now.
♪♪
-[Chuckling] Oh.
-Now Tang's really in love.
♪♪
Oh, now he's gonna play
some of the world's
most-loved melodies,
a la Zamfir.
[Flute plays]
[Monkey chitters]
-Let me amuse and cajole
your species.
Marta.
-He's Peter and the Wolf,
and the monkey,
and Ted and Alice.
♪♪
-Get me. I'm the master
of the pan flute.
-Linda like my friend Tiko?
-Yes, Tang.
-And the monkey, too?
-Linda like Tang's food?
-Yes.
♪♪
-Tang and Tiko --
they're cops.
♪♪
-Linda like Tang?
-Well, yeah, but I also
like other beverages
like Hi-C.
♪♪
Hey, wait a minute.
Whose legs are whose there?
♪♪
-Somebody's got frog legs.
-Oh, I'm gonna go
spank myself.
♪♪
-I will have to return
to my friends on the ship.
They will be worried for me.
-I'm gonna have to return
to my cold shower.
♪♪
-You like friends on ship
more than Tang!
-Yeah, I guess I do.
Why?
♪♪
-What you say is not true, Tang.
I love you.
Come on.
Help me with the presents.
-No!
-Ah, Tang's gonna take a powder.
Wait, Tang is a powder.
-[Laughs]
♪♪
-Linda!
Tang cannot swim!
-Oh.
-Tang will settle to bottom.
Must stir.
-You think Tang falling in watervery funny?
Maybe this funny, too?
-Aaaah!
-Russian judge gives it a 6.
-Nah, she didn't come
out of her tuck in time.
[Laughter]
-[Screams]
♪♪
-See no evil.
Well, maybe just a little.
Yeah.
-This week in The Enquirer --
Tang's recipe for love,
lots of good food,
and his water baby.
♪♪
-Ooh!
-That's what I call
a complete breakfast.
Tang, toast, milk, and fruit.
-And booty.
♪♪
-Hey, get out of the acid bath.
-There's so much to see,
so much to do!
-Your ship.
♪♪
-Hey, I can see your house
from here.
♪♪
-Yeah.
-So beautiful here.
-And it's not even real.
-Centaurus was once like this.
♪♪
What is it, Tang?
-They will take Linda away.
-And Tang, too.
-Actually,
it's New and Improved Tang.
-We'll go to
a new homeland together.
-No.
Mother and Father are here.
This is myhomeland.
♪♪
This is Linda's home.
-Yes, Tang.
-Tang's never heard
of a one-night stand.
♪♪
-But I have to tell the admiral.
-Why tell admiral?
-He's my friend.
He's like a father.
-[Coughs]
-The only one I've ever known.
-Ah, Lolita...
-Like your father?
♪♪
We will go to him.
-The frozen dad?
♪♪
-It's the monkeys.
Get outta there.
Scamper.
Cheese it.
-They're too busy spearing
to put anybody down.
♪♪
-Linda, across.
-Tang!
No!
-It's Tang kwan do.
♪♪
-Those, ladies and gentlemen,
are the planet's
fiercest warriors.
[Indistinct shouting]
Pathetic.
♪♪
-Hey, everybody,
I'm Bruce Lee.
♪♪
-Looks like the family from,
uh, "It's About Time."
-[Screams]
♪♪
Yeah, you're lucky
my chick's here, man.
♪♪
-He's fighting a bunch
of Sonny Bono look-alikes.
-Tang, get out!
♪♪
Doc, help.
Help.
-Linda!
Linda!
-Uhp, typical response.
They don't understand it,
so I better shoot it.
-[Screams]
-Cool.
-She's hysterical.
-Let me go!
-Here, hold her a second.
Let me go!
-Hey, he's giving her
a shot with a corkscrew.
♪♪
-Darn jocks always
taking my girl.
I'm gonna leave
this darn chess club.
-Why was she trying
to go back, Doc?
♪♪
-I'm sure that Scott
would have found him by now
if the wound
was really critical.
-I should have gone myself.
-Look, take it from me, David,
if that boy can be found,
Scott'll find him.
♪♪
-Bradley just reported in.
They've lost the trail.
Stopped suddenly
at the edge of a clip.
-There was a note.
It said, 'Aaah!'"
[Loud rumbling]
-Gee, what do you
think that means?
-Volcano's going to erupt.
This time, we won't be safe.
♪♪
Radio Mr. Scott
to return to ship.
♪♪
-Is it my breath?
-It ishis breath.
-[Speaking native language]
-All: What?!
-Try once more, Jung.
-[Speaking native language]
-Try something
that means something.
-I belive it's hopeless,
Commander.
-Admiral King wants us
to report back to the ship.
He's afraid Old Smokey over
there's gonna blow its top
and shake the walls
down to the canyon.
-No, you're thinking
of the Big, Bad Wolf.
-Alright.
Let's go.
♪♪
-Okay, I just stay here
and then I be here
if you need me.
♪♪
-[Speaking native language]
-Hey, it's Cliff Robertson.
Hi, I'm a mountain.
Stupid.
♪♪
[Rumbling]
-What are the chances
of the idol falling over?
-Billy Idol?
♪♪
-Uh-oh.
Stock footage and lots of it,
coming at us.
♪♪
-Sorry, sir.
-Hey, what were you doing
in the washing machine?
-How are those chicks
coming along?
Hatched yet?
-Mr. Scott.
Prepare the ship for departure.
-Yes, sir.
♪♪
-I hate you.
I hate all of you!
-Gee, don't say hi.
-Sergeant Nevins,
crew to stations.
-Yes, sir.
Attention all personnel --
ascend stations.
Ascend stations.
-Raise the ramp.
-Raise the rent?
Hey, I've got a lease, pal.
-Linda!
-Hold it, Nevins!
♪♪
-More stock footage.
Hit the deck.
-What is that?
-Linda!
Linda!
♪♪
-Thwow them to the gwound,
pwanet, most woughwy.
Thank you.
♪♪
-Oh, I hit my butt.
It's all hot,
and it hurts and stuff.
Ow.
-Uh, let me fall down
one more time.
♪♪
Guys, I got a feeling
it's call-back time.
There's a girl down that well.
-But the chicks are done.
-Is anyone in
the washing machine?
-Where's Tang, anyway?
♪♪
-Zzz-z-z-z!
-This is no time
for push-ups, you dolt.
♪♪
-Get the ship outta
here, Mr. Scott.
-Good thing I've got
my Farah action slacks on.
-Linda!
Linda!
♪♪
-Magnet.
Hey, I can't finish
my jumble puzzle.
♪♪
-Lin--
You get back to the ship!
That's an order!
-We're both going back!
-I can't leave her here.
-Then let go of me.
-Look, leave me here.
I have to find her!
Don't you understand?
She's my responsibility.
She's all I have.
Linda's my daughter.
-Uh-oh.
-Geez.
Talk about deus ex machina.
♪♪
-Huh?
-Yellowstone.
♪♪
Boy, they're really
rocking that place.
-This is what happens after
you eat at Lollapalooza.
♪♪
Looks like the land
at Dairy Queen.
♪♪
-Well, fire up the wok.
Dinner's ruined again.
♪♪
-Hey! Look out!
The Styrofoam's on fire!
-Zzzzzzzz-z-z-z!
[Rumbling stops]
-Huh?
♪♪
-Zzz-z-z-z!
-Tang?
-Well, this is great.
I feel like E.T.
-Tang?
♪♪
Tang?!
-I'm back.
Hi, girl.
-Zz-z-z!
-[Yells as Tarzan]
♪♪
-Remember when we were dating,
and we met right here
at this pool of filth?
♪♪
-This is great.
She can meet his frozen parents.
-Tang!
Oh, Tang.
-Linda.
♪♪
-Let's make some static
with these pelts.
♪♪
You still haven't
scrubbed your pits.
That's okay. I love you,
you big breakfast drink.
♪♪
-Come on.
I've really changed the place.
Uh, the monkey moved in.
I hope that doesn't bother you.
♪♪
-Why is this called
"Planet of the
Prehistoric Women"?
It makes no sense.
-Zzz-z-z-z!
-Alright, Sergeant.
Standby vertical gravitators.
-Yes, sir.
-Boy, they really got
a lot done on that planet.
Whoo.
-Hold it, Scott.
They're alive, Admiral.
Linda and the boy.
Look.
-Attention all personnel.
Attention. Attention.
-Oh, hey, Elvis.
-Linda is alive.
-I'd like to sing
some of my hits,
and then I'm going down
to the galley to have some
peanut-butter-and-banana
sandwich.
-Standby, men.
-You, too, Elvis.
-Well, Mr. Scott...
let's get about going home.
-You mean we're not going
back for them, Admiral?
-No, we'll not go back.
-Not today.
-They'll be happy here.
They belong here.
They belong to each other.
-Who are you?
Chuck Woolery?
-Together, they'll create
a world of their own.
-I'm feeling loud,
proud, and brassy.
-...from their homeland.
-Except for the master race.
-I'm sure you're right,
you heartless bastard.
-Activate controls.
-Yes, sir.
♪♪
-The admiral's a different man.
-Yes.
-I know our affair wasn't
set up from this film,
but let's be part ofthe loose ends festival, anyhow.
♪♪
-[Imitates monkey]
-Oh, look, you can see my house.
♪♪
-Drive me to the mall.
-We got a planet
to populate, honey.
-I'm already bored, Tang.
♪♪
-Zzz-z-z-z!
-Mr. Scott.
Make an entry in the ship's log.
-[Speaking gibberish]
-...is retiring
from the third planet
of the Solaris system.
As this planet was here
before unknown...
-Talking real fast,
like you know what
you're talking about, yes.
-From this day forward,
third planet of Solaris
will be known
as the blue planet.
We designate it Planet...
Earth.
-Earth?
-Oh, come on.
Who made you God?
-Oh, man evolved
from Tang, right.
We better get out of here.
-That means we better go.
-That means my great
great-grandmother
was really, really hot.
-Was she?
-We got to go figure out a way
to change ourselves back.
-You have a picture?
♪♪
[Doors creak]
[Doors whir]
[Doors thud and clank]
-Hey, you know what?
These, uh --
Ugh, these Isaac Asimov
sideburns come off.
-They're just taped on.
-They're phony.
-Oh, that's what it means
to be Isaac Asimov, I guess.
-Yeah, but he probably
already thought of that.
-Yeah.
Instead of a doomsday machine,
I guess it kind of turned out
to be a dorks-day machine.
-Well, it could be worse.
-Oh?
-Could have been
a Doris Day machine.
-[Laughs] Oh.
-Good...
-Come on, you guys.
It's time to read
some letters here.
Cambot, let's...
Oops.
You lost your head.
-That was my skull.
-Oh, that's too bad.
That's okay.
-Alright.
Here we go, Cambot.
Put that up on the screen.
"MST 3000, I'm writing
a response to you guys,
and one episode in specific.
I believe 'Robot Holocaust'
was the name.
The one in which a man
possessed valuable knowledge,
and was transformed
into a vegetable-like being
because of his inability
to cooperate."
-Avocado Boy.
-Yep.
-Yeah.
-And we had a contest
to see who could come upwith a name for the avocado guy,
and here's his entry.
He's the winner, by the way.
Here, he gave us four.
Skip the Couch Potato.
Let's have a picture
of that guy, Cambot.
-You call me.
-A Man from P.R.O.D.U.C.E.
A Weeble-O Named Chloro-Phil.
And The Eighth Wonder
of the Guacamole.
-[Laughs]
-So, that's from...
James S. Calstrom, Bloomington.
-The winner of the brainstorm.
-Yeah, he won the brainstorm.
Thanks, all who entered
that one, by the way,
and here's this next one.
"Dear Sir or 'Bot,
one lonely, depressing
Saturday night,
I happened to switch
to Channel 49,
and found 'MST 3000.'
It was love at first laugh.
I was instantly hooked.
Now my life has meaning."
-That's pretty sad, really.
-"Anyway, it's a great show.
I've shown it
to several of my friends,
and they say they all like it.
Even my wife likes it,
and she is not an SF fan."
What's SF mean?
-Uh, San Francisco.
-Oh, okay.
-Anyway, the last one here isfrom a father and daughter team.
-Do they dance, too?
-I don't know.
"We would like information
about the fan club.
We would also like to know
if there's a special club group
for Tom Servo."
-You betcha.
-Wow.
"Ever since his head exploded
trying to think
of something good to say
about 'The Bride Vanishes,'
we realized he has a rare
and special honesty.
It's good that you didn't ask
for good comments about
'Project Moon Base' --
the consequences
would be unthinkable."
That's from Ken--
-I shutter at the thought.
-Yeah, Kenneth J. Plotkin
and Sarah E. Plotkin,
the Plotkin Family Bellringers.
Well, that's it.
-The Family Plotkin.
Tom Servo, you want to give them
the mailing address?
-Sure.
-Cambot, put it up
on the screen, there.
-Love to. It's the
"Mystery Science Theater 3000"
Information Club.
PO Box 5325, Hopkins,
Minnesota 55343.
-Alright, that's the end
of the experiment.
What do you think, sirs?
-♪ I think I'll file
this thing for you ♪
♪ As I always seem to do
♪ I like working
for you, Clay ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
a really neat guy ♪
-Well, I think
you should file this, Larry.
-'Kay.
-Ahh.
Until next time, pasty boy.
♪♪